Guide to the Henry S. Huntington Family Papers
Yale University Divinity School Library
- General Correspondence, 1857-1924, n.d.; Series II
  - Correspondence to/from Henry Strong Huntington
    - I-J, 1867-1904 (Box 30, Folder 397)
    - Irish, J.P., 1886-1888 (Box 30, Folder 398)
    - Jones, Frank. C., 1862-1869 (Box 31, Folder 399)
    - Jones, Frank C., 1870-1875 (Box 31, Folder 400)
    - Jones, Frank C., 1876-1880 (Box 31, Folder 401)
    - Jones, Frank C., 1887-1892 (Box 31, Folder 402)
    - Jones, Frank C., 1893-1898 (Box 31, Folder 403)
    - Jones, Frank C., 1899-1906 (Box 31, Folder 404)
    - Jones, Frank C., 1907, n.d. (Box 31, Folder 405)
    - Jones, Frank C. (fragments), 1892, n.d. (Box 31, Folder 406)
    - Jones, Harriet L., 1909, 1912, n.d. (Box 31, Folder 407)
    - K, 1864-1913, n.d. (Box 31, Folder 408)
    - Kellogg, E.M., 1871 (Box 32, Folder 409)
    - Ketchum, Silas, 1871 (Box 32, Folder 409)
    - Knapp, Geo. P., 1904 (Box 32, Folder 409)
    - L, 1869-1919, n.d. (Box 32, Folder 410)
    - Lawrence, Rt. Rev. William, 1897 (Box 32, Folder 411)
    - Leeds, S.P., 1869-1870 (Box 32, Folder 411)
    - [Loba?], Fred, 1875-1876 (Box 32, Folder 411)
    - Ma-Me, 1862-1916, n.d. (Box 32, Folder 412)
    - Mi-Mu, 1869-1916, n.d. (Box 32, Folder 413)
    - Machias, [ME?], (Center Street Church), 1888 (Box 32, Folder 414)
    - Matthews-Richardson, Elizabeth, 1907-1917 (Box 32, Folder 414)
    - McCully, Josephine Tucker, 1905-1917 (Box 32, Folder 414)
    - Mead, C.M., 1869-1916, n.d. (Box 32, Folder 415)
    - Meriam, Sarah C., 1891-1906, n.d. (Box 32, Folder 416)
    - Milford, NH, (First Congregational Church), 1872 (Box 32, Folder 416)
    - Milton, MA, (Congregational Church), 1889-1906 (Box 32, Folder 417)
    - Monroe, Gertrude and Moses, 1899-1919 (Box 32, Folder 418)
    - N, 1865-1901, n.d. (Box 32, Folder 419)
    - National Council of Congregational Churches, 1916-1919 (Box 32, Folder 420)
    - Newtown, CT, (Congregational Church), 1864 (Box 32, Folder 421)
    - Northrop, Cyrus, 1900-1914 (Box 32, Folder 421)
    - O, 1865-1916, n.d. (Box 32, Folder 422)
    - P, 1863-1917, n.d. (Box 32, Folder 423)
    - Palmer, Charles Ray, 1900-1910 (Box 32, Folder 424)
    - Pratt, Lewellyn, 1865-1898 (Box 32, Folder 424)
    - Preston, Abel, 1863-1866 (Box 32, Folder 425)
    - Preston, Alice, 1866 (Box 32, Folder 425)
    - Preston, H.W., 1868-1869 (Box 32, Folder 425)
    - Preston, Jane, 1864-1890 (Box 32, Folder 425)
    - Preston, Edward W., 1863-1870, n.d. (Box 32, Folder 426)
    - R, 1871 (Box 32, Folder 427)
    - R, 1864-1909, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 428)
    - Riggs, Henry, Emma Mary, 1913 (Box 33, Folder 429)
    - Robert College, 1909 (Box 33, Folder 429)
    - Rolfe, Martha, 1890-1918 (Box 33, Folder 429)
    - Sa-So, 1864-1910, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 430)
    - Sp-Sy, 1861-1916, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 431)
    - Savage, Wm. S., 1867-1871, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 432)
    - Seaborn, Anna, 1911, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 433)
    - Smith, Albert Ellen, 1908-1917, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 433)
    - Strong, Augustus H., 1888-1918 (Box 33, Folder 433)
    - T, 1866-1914, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 434)
    - Teele, Albert K., 1892-1901 (Box 33, Folder 435)
    - Temperance Societies, 1892-1893 (Box 33, Folder 435)
    - Thompson, Mary W., 1865-1866 (Box 33, Folder 436)
    - Thompson, R.B., 1864-1870 (Box 33, Folder 436)
    - Tower, Harriet E., 1861-1870 (Box 33, Folder 437)
    - Trowbridge, Luther S., 1865-1897 (Box 33, Folder 438)
    - Tucker, Arthur H., 1892-1904 (Box 33, Folder 438)
    - Tucker, Herbert, 1891-1906 (Box 33, Folder 438)
    - V, 1889, 1893, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 439)
    - Wa-We, 1868-1918, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 440)
    - Wh-Wy, 1865-1913, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 441)
    - Warner, NH, (Congregational Church), 1864-1877, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 442)
    - Warren, W., 1863-1891 (Box 33, Folder 443)
    - Waterman, John A., 1887-1911 (Box 33, Folder 444)
    - Waterman, Lucy D., 1902, 1907 (Box 34, Folder 445)
    - Waterman, Mary E., 1888-1919, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 445)
    - Wheeler, A.M., 1862, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 446)
    - Wheeler, Carolyn S., 1872-1907 (Box 34, Folder 446)
    - Wheeler, M.D., 1864-1876 (Box 34, Folder 446)
    - White, Catherine P., 1890-1903 (Box 34, Folder 447)
    - Wilcox, A.H., 1864-1913 (Box 34, Folder 447)
    - Williams, Sherman, 1874-1875, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 448)
    - Williston, Martin L., 1866-1918 (Box 34, Folder 448)
    - Woodin, Samuel F., 1871 (Box 34, Folder 448)
    - Y, 1867-1911 (Box 34, Folder 449)
    - Yale University, 1863-1886 (Box 34, Folder 450)
    - Young, Frances E., 1899-1914 (Box 34, Folder 451)
    - Ziegler, Clara, 1908, 1918, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 452)
    - First Name Only, 1895-1914, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 453)
    - Illegible/Anonymous, 1864-1915, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 454)
  - Correspondence to/from Mary L. H. Huntington
    - A, 1866-1920, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 455)
    - Ashmond, Katherine, 1870 (Box 34, Folder 456)
    - Ba-Be, 1866-1910, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 457)
    - Bi-Bu, 1871-1921, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 458)
    - Barnum, Helen R., 1907-1911 (Box 34, Folder 459)
    - Barnum, Mary, 1903, 1911 (Box 34, Folder 459)
    - Barnes, Kittie B.W., 1864-1873 (Box 34, Folder 460)
    - Bean, Harriet A., 1873-1907 (Box 34, Folder 461)
    - Beckwith, V. Eugenie, 1881-1909 (Box 34, Folder 462)
    - Bush, Caroline E., 1899-1906 (Box 34, Folder 463)
    - Butyka, Makareed, 1904 (Box 34, Folder 463)
    - C, 1841-1921, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 464)
    - Canfield, Sarah B., 1864-1910 (Box 34, Folder 465)
    - Cousens, F.G., 1879-1898, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 466)
    - D, 1878-1922, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 467)
    - E, 1891-1923, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 468)
    - F, 1861-1916, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 469)
    - Fox, Julia (Brown), 1864-1875, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 470)
    - G, 1872-1923, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 471)
    - Gordon, Annie E., 1920-1924 (Box 35, Folder 472)
    - H, 1870-1916, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 473)
    - Hale, Ella R., 1889-1924 (Box 34, Folder 474)
    - Harris, Mary, 1874, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 475)
    - Holmes, Margaret H., 1891-1899 (Box 34, Folder 475)
    - Hubbard, Helen, 1871-1879, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 475)
    - Huntington, 1883-1911, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 476)
    - J, 1877, 1922, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 477)
    - Jones, Frank C., 1883 (Box 35, Folder 478)
    - Jones, Harriet, 1912-1923 (Box 35, Folder 478)
    - K, 1871-1919, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 479)
    - Kennedy, Rev. Phineas, 1923 (Box 35, Folder 480)
    - Kinney, Mary E., 1909 (Box 35, Folder 480)
    - Kirkton, Ethel B., 1908-1917, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 481)
    - Knapp, Anna J., 1907, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 481)
    - L, 1878-1921 (Box 35, Folder 482)
    - Lass, John, 1884-1914, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 483)
    - Lincoln, Jeanine W., 1899-1921, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 484)
    - Long, Elizabeth (Lizzie) H., 1865-1924, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 485)
    - Loud, Mary L., 1899-1911 (Box 36, Folder 486)
    - M, 1869-1923 (Box 36, Folder 487)
    - Martin, Laura A. K., 1865-1870, n.d. (Box 36, Folder 488)
    - Matchett, Cornelia F., 1882-1892, n.d. (Box 36, Folder 489)
    - Matthews-Richardson, Elizabeth, 1911, 1923, n.d. (Box 36, Folder 490)
    - Meriam, Sarah C., 1890-1923 (Box 36, Folder 491)
    - Meriam, Sarah C., n.d. (Box 36, Folder 492)
    - Monroe, Gertrude (McKinney), 1898-1921, n.d. (Box 36, Folder 493)
    - N, 1898-1920, n.d. (Box 36, Folder 494)
    - Newhall, Julia F., 1885-1890 (Box 36, Folder 495)
    - O, 1877, 1924 (Box 36, Folder 496)
    - P, 1871-1923, n.d. (Box 36, Folder 497)
    - Quick, John S., 1883-1915, n.d. (Box 36, Folder 498)
    - R, 1890-1924, n.d. (Box 36, Folder 499)
    - Riggs, Charles T., 1937 (Box 36, Folder 500)
    - Rolfe, Elizabeth, 1886-1923, n.d. (Box 36, Folder 500)
    - Rolfe, Martha, 1912-1920 (Box 36, Folder 501)
    - Rowe, Hettie M., 1892-1898 (Box 36, Folder 501)
    - S, 1870-1924, n.d. (Box 36, Folder 502)
    - Sanders, Florence, 1868-1887 (Box 36, Folder 503)
    - Sculpham, J. R., 1862-1868 (Box 36, Folder 503A, B)
    - Smith, Caroline F., 1878-1891 (Box 36, Folder 504)
    - Smith, Ellen T., 1914-1924 (Box 36, Folder 504)
    - T, 1884-1924 (Box 37, Folder 505)
    - Thayer, Jane, 1899-1907 (Box 37, Folder 506)
    - Thompson, Rhoda, 1873-1923 (Box 37, Folder 506)
    - U-V, 1893, 1909, n.d. (Box 37, Folder 507)
    - Van Zandt, Elsie, 1921-1924 (fragment) (Box 37, Folder 508)
    - W, 1868-1921, n.d. (Box 37, Folder 509)
    - Wadsworth, Ellen M., 1891-1909, n.d. (Box 37, Folder 510)
    - Walker Missionary Home, n.d. (Box 37, Folder 510)
    - Ward, M.E., 1876-1890 (Box 37, Folder 511)
    - Waterman, Mary E., 1888-1891 (Box 37, Folder 512)
    - Waterman, Mary E., 1892-1923, n.d. (Box 37, Folder 513)
    - Webster, Mattie (Farnham), 1877-1880 (Box 37, Folder 514)
    - Webster, Mattie (Farnham), 1881-1924, n.d. (Box 37, Folder 515)
    - Weeks, Angie, 1890, 1924 (Box 37, Folder 516)
    - Weeks, Mary Grace, 1891-1923, n.d. (Box 37, Folder 516)
    - Whittemore, Alma R., 1917-1924 (Box 37, Folder 517)
    - Williston, Louise S., 1876-1889 (Box 37, Folder 518)
    - Williston, Louise S., 1890-1921, n.d. (Box 37, Folder 519)
    - Winn, Sila C., 1878 (Box 38, Folder 520)
    - Women's Board of Missions, 1877 (Box 38, Folder 520)
    - Women's Union Christian Colleges (Orient), 1922 (Box 38, Folder 520)
    - Wood, Susan, 1867-1870, n.d. (Box 38, Folder 521)
    - Young, Frances E., 1907-1924, n.d. (Box 38, Folder 522)
    - Ziegler, 1909, n.d. (Box 38, Folder 522)
    - First Name Only, 1880-1924, n.d. (Box 38, Folder 523)
    - Illegible/anonymous, 1887-1921, n.d. (Box 38, Folder 524)
    - Unidentified Correspondence, 1846, 1852, n.d. (Box 38, Folder 525)
    - Unidentified Fragments, 1902, n.d. (Box 38, Folder 526)
- Writings, 1851-1931, n.d; Series III
  - HSH - Sermons, 1860-1904 (Box 39, Folder 527-535)
  - HSH - Sermons, 1904-1920, n.d. (Box 40, Folder 536-545)
  - HSH - Sermon Notes, 1860-1920, n.d. (Box 41, Folder 546-552)
  - HSH - Sermon Notes, n.d. (Box 42, Folder 553-556)
  - HSH-Church Material, 1884-1906 (Box 43, Folder 557)
  - Writings by Children, 1921, 1931, n.d. (Box 43, Folder 558)
  - HSH Compositions, 1851-1852, n.d. (Box 43, Folder 559)
  - HSH Debates, 1851-1853, n.d. (Box 43, Folder 560-561)
  - HSH Compositions, 1852-1857, n.d. (Box 43, Folder 562-563)
  - HSH- "The Life of Samuel Huntington", handwritten draft (Box 43, Folder 564)
  - HSH- "The Life of Samuel Huntington", n.d. (Box 43, Folder 565)
  - HSH- Biography of Samuel Huntington, n.d. (Box 43, Folder 566)
  - HSH-source material for "The Life of Samuel Huntington", n.d. (Box 43, Folder 567)
  - HSH-source material for "The Life of Samuel Huntington", n.d. (Box 44, Folder 568-569)
  - HSH-articles, 1876-1913 (Box 44, Folder 570)
  - HSH-Norfolk Conference of Congragational Charters, Report of Missionary Commission, 1902 (Box 44, Folder 571)
  - HSH-Writings, 1895, n.d. (Box 44, Folder 572)
  - HSH-Misc.: Praise Meetings, Eventide Services, Tangents, lists, 1895-1925 (Box 44, Folder 573)
  - MLH-Writings, 1895, n.d. (Box 44, Folder 574)
  - MLH-Writings, n.d. (Box 44, Folder 575)
  - MLH-Essays, n.d. (Box 44, Folder 576)
  - MLH-Essays, 1858, n.d. (Box 44, Folder 577)
  - George-writings, 1892 (Box 45, Folder 578)
  - Charles Zeigler-writings (source material for Hymnal), 1900-1911, n.d. (Box 45, Folder 579)
  - HSH-Notebooks, 1856-1861, 1870-1904 (Box 45, Folder 580-585)
  - HSH-Notebook, n.d. (Box 46, Folder 586)
  - HSH-text notes (sample), n.d. (Box 46, Folder 587)
  - HSH-text notes, n.d. (Box 46, Folder 588)
  - HSH-text notes (index rerum) (Box 46, Folder 589)
  - MLH-Notebooks, 1895-1896, 1898, n.d. (Box 46, Folder 590)
- Biographical Documentation, 1849-1949, n.d; Series IV
  - Datebooks/Journals-HSH, 1852-1890 (Box 47, Folder 591-597)
  - Datebooks/Journals-HSH, 1891 (Box 48, Folder 598)
  - Datebooks/Journals-HSH, 1893 -1907 (Box 48, Folder 598-599)
  - Datebooks/Journals-HSH, 1905-1907 (Box 48, Folder 599)
  - Notebooks/Journals-HSH, 1910-1912 (Box 48, Folder 599-600)
  - Datebooks/Journals-MLH, 1891-1924, n.d. (Box 48, Folder 601-603)
  - Datebook/Journal-George Herbert, 1881 (Box 49, Folder 604)
  - Genealogical Material, 1857-1922, n.d. (Box 49, Folder 605)
  - Accounts/Record Books-HSH, 1849-1853 (Box 49, Folder 606)
  - Church Records-HSH, 1872-1876 (Box 49, Folder 607)
  - Accounts of Hobart Fund at Milton, 1892-1908 (Box 49, Folder 608)
  - Accounts/Records (bills, receipts)-HSH/MLH, 1862-1912, n.d. (Box 49, Folder 609)
  - Accounts/Records (bills, receipts)-HSH, 1853-1857 (at Yale) (Box 49, Folder 610)
  - Accounts/Record Books-Mrs. Herbert, 1882-1885 (Box 49, Folder 611)
  - Guestbook-HSH/MLH, 1904-1910 (Box 49, Folder 612)
  - Account Books-MLH, 1905 (Box 49, Folder 613)
  - Account/Record Books-MLH, 1900-1905 (Box 49, Folder 614)
  - Accounts/Record Books-MLH, 1906-1913 (Box 49, Folder 614)
  - Accounts/Record Books, Letters-MLH, 1899-1902 (Box 49, Folder 615)
  - Accounts/Record Books, Letters-MLH, 1903-1905 (Box 49, Folder 615)
  - Accounts/Record Books-MLH, 1886, 1889, 1894-99 (Box 49, Folder 616)
  - Accounts/Record Books-MLH, 1880-81, 1892-93 (Box 49, Folder 616)
  - Account/Record Books-MLH, 1890-1891 (Box 49, Folder 616)
  - Biographical Material-HSH, 1849-1909, n.d. (Box 50, Folder 617)
  - HSH/MLH Passports, 1909 (Box 50, Folder 618)
  - School Merit Awards, c. 1840 (Box 50, Folder 619)
  - Programs, 1871-1899 (Box 50, Folder 620)
  - Programs, 1900-1911, n.d. (Box 50, Folder 621)
  - Andover Theological Seminary, 1860, 1915, n.d. (Box 50, Folder 622)
  - Yale University, 1888-1910 (Box 50, Folder 623)
  - Clippings, 1851-1893 (Box 50, Folder 624)
  - Church Manuals, 1860-1887 (Box 50, Folder 625)
  - Fraternal Organizations, 1895-1905, n.d. (Box 50, Folder 626)
  - Biographical Material-MLH, 1857-1907 (Box 50, Folder 627)
  - Biographical Material-MLH (Children's Notebook "Going over things from Mothers Desk"), 1929, August (Box 51, Folder 628)
  - Biographical Material-Children, 1895-1897, n.d. (Box 51, Folder 629)
  - Biographical Material-Cornelia/Theron, 1890-1949, n.d. (Box 51, Folder 630)
  - Biographical Material-Theresa, 1896, 1913, n.d. (Box 51, Folder 631)
  - Biographical Material-Ellsworth, 1902-1949, n.d. (Box 51, Folder 632)
  - Biographical Material-George, 1890-1923 (Box 51, Folder 633)
  - Biographical Material-Harry, 1892-1915, n.d. (Box 51, Folder 634)
  - Biographical Material-Ruth, 1899-1903 (Box 51, Folder 635)
  - Biographical Material-OEH, 1877, n.d. (Box 51, Folder 636)
  - Biographical Material-Herbert, 1805-1890, n.d. (Box 51, Folder 637)
  - Biographical Material-Gaytes, Carol Theresa (Herbert), 1869, n.d. (Box 51, Folder 638)
  - Biographical Material-Memorial of Susan (Hunt.) Perkins, 1879 (Box 51, Folder 638)
  - Photos/Portraits, n.d. (Box 51, Folder 639)
  - Photos/Portraits, n.d. (Box 51, Folder 640)
  - Portraits, n.d. (Box 51, Folder 641)
  - Group Photos, n.d. (Box 52, Folder 642)
  - Harry's Yale class of 1904, n.d. (Box OV-d4)
  - Photos (houses, churches, travel in U. S., etc.), n.d. (Box 52, Folder 643)
  - Photos (travel in Persia, Near East), ca. 1903 (Box 52, Folder 643A)
- Collected Material, 1827-1926, n.d; Series V
  - Portraits (identified), n.d. (Box 53, Folder 644-648)
  - Group Photos, n.d. (Box 53, Folder 649)
  - Photos (scenic), n.d. (Box 53, Folder 650)
  - Prints (scenic), n.d. (Box 54, Folder 651-652)
  - Prints (religious), n.d. (Box 54, Folder 653)
  - Prints /Postcards, n.d. (Box 54, Folder 654)
  - Prints/Postcards, n.d. (Box 54, Folder 655)
  - Nancy Fanning Bushwell's Scrapbook (HSH's great-aunt), 1827-1864 (Box 54, Folder 656)
  - Advertisements/Catalogues, 1880-1926, n.d. (Box 54, Folder 657)
  - Andover Controversy-clippings, 1908-1909, n.d. (Box 54, Folder 658)
  - Programs-Church Services, 1881-1898 (Box 55, Folder 659)
  - Programs-Church Services, 1899-1922, n.d. (Box 55, Folder 660)
  - Programs-Performances, Graduation Exercises, 1886-1894 (Box 55, Folder 661)
  - Programs-Performances, Graduations, 1895-1929, n.d. (Box 55, Folder 662-664)
  - Pamphlets-Cooking, 1911-1922, n.d. (Box 55, Folder 665)
  - Advertisements, 1878-1917, n.d. (Box 56, Folder 666)
  - Letters by and about Missionaries, 1889-1913, n.d. (Box 56, Folder 667)
  - Civil War Letters, 1862, n.d. (Box 56, Folder 668)
  - Church Polity and Practice, 1895, n.d. (Box 56, Folder 669)
  - Yale Printed Material, 1855-1910 (Box 56, Folder 670)
  - Clipping-Mary C. Bartlett (Sample from discarded scrapbook), 1880-1915, n.d. (Box 56, Folder 671)
  - Clippings-Christianity, Missions, 1876-1925, n.d. (Box 56, Folder 672)
  - Clippings-American Board/Rockefeller Controversy, 1905, n.d. (Box 56, Folder 673)
  - Clippings, 1879-1923, n.d. (Box 56, Folder 674-676)
  - Invitations/Announcements, 1859-1883 (Box 56, Folder 677-678)
  - Invitations/Announcements, 1909-1914 (Box 57, Folder 679)
  - Invitations-Wedding Graduation, 1884-1898 (Box 57, Folder 680)
  - Invitations/Announcements, 1915-1924, n.d. (Box 57, Folder 681-682)
  - Associations/Solicitations, n.d. (Box 57, Folder 683)
  - Union Library Association membership/ HSH, 1903. (Box OV-d4)
  - Calling Cards/Business Cards, n.d. (Box 57, Folder 684-685)
  - Cards, n.d. (Box 58, Folder 686)
  - Cards-greeting, n.d. (Box 58, Folder 687)
  - Cards-devotional, n.d. (Box 58, Folder 688)
  - Cards-Easter, n.d. (Box 58, Folder 689)
  - Irvine, Julia Josephine-"War-Time Letters from France", 1914-1917 (Box 58, Folder 690)
  - School Books-Grammatical Institutes, HSH's Portsmouth Sunday School Hymn Book, MLH's Primary Object Lessons, 1840, 1862, n.d. (Box 58, Folder 691)
  - Sample Travel Book, n.d. (Box 59, Folder 692)
  - Miniature New Testaments, 1842, 1848 (Box 59, Folder 693)
  - Miniature Devotional Books, 1830, 1831, 1840, 1847, n.d. (Box 59, Folder 694)
  - Miscellaneous Devotional Items, 1893-1922, n.d. (Box 59, Folder 695)
  - Miscellaneous, 1860-1921, n.d. (Box 59, Folder 696-697)
  - Notes-MLH, n.d. (Box 60, Folder 698)
  - Notes-HSH, 1890-1916, n.d. (Box 60, Folder 699)
  - MLH Peabody to Family, 1850, 1855 (Box 60, Folder 700)
  - Miscellaneous Notes, 1879-1909, n.d. (Box 60, Folder 701)
  - Handcrafted cross (Box 60, Folder 702)
  - Miscellaneous, n.d. (Box 60, Folder 703)
  - Personal Items-Handkerchiefs, Pins, Embroidery, Buttons (Box 61, Folder 704)
  - Gift from HSH to MLH, Box of Positive Sayings, n.d. (Box 61, Folder 705)